Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Walter B. Wriston Papers
1918 -- 2008
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Wriston, Walter B.
MS134
30.73 Linear Feet 32 letter size document boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 6 record cartons, 2 legal size document boxes, 1 half letter size document box, 1 half legal size document box
1 Volumes
111 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
The collection consists of nine series: Speeches; Books; Articles and Interviews; Audiovisual Media; Subject Files; Photographs; Awards and Recognitions; Computer Spreadsheets; and Unprocessed Accessions.
Custodial History
The collection was donated by Mr. Wriston's wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, and his family. The collection consists of materials from his office at Citibank on Park Avenue in New York. They were arranged by Kurt Willet and shipped to the archives via UPS in three installments. The files from his office and personal computers were extracted and burned to a CD-ROM which was also included in the collection. His wife, Kathryn Wriston, later sent another package containing two copies of "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World" and "Risk and Other Four-Letter Words."
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials from Walter B. Wriston's office at Citibank on Park Avenue in New York. The bulk of the material dates to the 1980s and 1990s and includes both paper and electronic media.
The majority of the materials consist of source materials for and drafts of Wriston's three books "Risk and Other Four-Letter Words" (1986), "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World" (1992) and "Bites, Bytes, & Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement In a Wireless World" (2007). Also included are a nearly comprehensive collection of speeches and articles about banking, finance, and technology written by Wriston throughout his career. Wriston's career and interests are also documented in a substantial collection of audiovisual media and photographs. Subject files contain organizational records, special event materials, Wriston's 'inspiration' files, memorial and funereal material, and extensive correspondence. Awards recognizing Wriston's accomplishments include the Presidential Medal of Freedom (2004), as well a letter from President Ronald Reagan and letters of condolence from President George W. Bush.
Also included are the computer spreadsheets which document the original order of the computer files on each of Wriston's three computers. For more information about how the computer print-outs were processed, see the series-level note for series 008, as well as collection documentation. Collection documentation also includes the inventory of the Wriston archival material retained by the Citibank Archives.
Biographical / Historical
Walter B. Wriston (1889-1978) was born in Middletown, Connecticut, on August 3, 1919 to Dr. Henry Merritt Wriston and Ruth Colton Bigelow. Dr. Wriston graduated from the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University in 1942. Dr. Wriston is best known for serving as the CEO of Citicorp and its subsidiary, Citibank. Wriston graduated from Wesleyan University in 1941. Following his time at Fletcher, Wriston worked for a year as a U.S. State Department officer, and then pursued a four-year tour with the U.S. Army during World War II. Wriston joined Citibank in 1946 as a junior inspector in the Comptroller's Division. He was assigned to the National Division of Citibank in 1949, and was promoted several times over the next seven years, becoming the Vice President of the division in 1954. In 1956, Wriston joined Citibank's Overseas Division. A series of promotions resulted, and Wriston was named a Senior Vice President in 1958, the head of the Overseas Division in 1959, and Executive Vice President in 1960. Wriston became President of Citibank in 1967, and subsequently held the same titles over Citicorp when it was formed as Citibank's parent corporation in 1968. Wriston was promoted from President to Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Citibank in 1970, and instituted many innovations during these years, including the installation of automatic teller machines, as well as credit cards. Starting in the 1960's, Wriston held positions in several external organizations, including directorships over General Mills, General Electric Company, and Reuters Holdings PLC. Wriston was Chairman of President Reagan's Economic Policy Advisory Board, a member and former Chairman of The Business Council, and a former co-Chairman and Policy committee member of the Business Roundtable. He was a Trustee of the Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, a Life Governor of New York Presbyterian Hospital, and a Fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences. During his years as CEO of Citicorp, Wriston was awarded honorary degrees from Brown University, Columbia University, and New York University. Wriston also began the practice of lecturing at business schools and academic institutions during this time, specializing in economics and the impact of information technology on the banking technology. His expertise lead him to testify before the U.S. Senate Committees, acting as a representative of Citibank and other banks. On September 1, 1984, Wriston retired as Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Citicorp and its subsidiary, Citibank. After his retirement, Wriston continued to lecture at academic institutions, and published three books: Risk and Other Four Letter Words (1986), The Twilight of Sovereignty (1992), and Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement In a Wireless World (posth., 2007). Wriston also continued to receive several honors post retirement, including the Medal of Freedom by President George W. Bush on June 23, 2004. Wriston married his first wife, Barbara Brengle, in 1942. After her death in 1966, he married Kathryn Ann Dineen in March of 1968. He had one daughter, and two grandchildren. In his personal life, he was the member of several clubs, including the Links Club, the River Club of New York, and the Palm Beach Bath and Tennis Club. Wriston passed away on January 19, 2005 in New York City.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Walter B. Wriston; Alumni collections; Finance; Citicorp
- Speeches, 1951 -- 2003; 1980 -- 1999; MS134.001; 8.0 Linear Feet; 24 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains speeches written by Walter B. Wriston. The speeches span from 1951-2003 with the bulk of the speeches from the 1980s. The speeches were produced for an assortment of engagements, such as Citigroup/Citibank events and meetings; lectures and commencement ceremonies at schools and universities; retirement dinners and introductions; Business Council meetings; testimony before U.S. Federal/State Committees; testimony or remarks at the European and U.S. Chamber of Commerce; Committee and Board of Trustee meetings; conferences; club meetings; association meetings; and the Bank Forum. Pamphlet versions of some speeches were published by First National City Bank (Citibank/Citigroup) and are included with the corresponding speech. In addition, there is material relating to speaking engagements, such as correspondence, conference packets, travel arrangements, thank you letters, slides, and notes.
  Speech titles are followed by the date on which Wriston gave a particular speech. For speeches that included a date range, the date on which Wriston actually gave the speech is in the notes field. The folders often contain multiple copies of the speeches including rough drafts, final drafts, and back-up copies. Some of the speeches are printed out files extracted from Wriston's computer. Titles in brackets indicate a final publication title followed by Wriston's original computer file name. Wriston's original computer file names were preserved. When a file date did not correspond to the actual date of the speech, the date of the speech was added.
  Arrangement
  The speeches are arranged chronologically. Materials accessioned and processed in 2009 are arranged in a second chronological run at the end of the series.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Comments about the Eclectic Society of Phi Nu Theta at Wesleyan University, 1951; MS134.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Walter B. Wriston was a member of the Eclectic Society of Phi Nu Theta which is a fraternity at Wesleyan University.
  - Remarks at Correspondent Bank Forum, 1959-02-07; MS134.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Brazil, Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00003; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 1)
    Brazil Politics and government; Brazil Economic policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Cuba, Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Mexico, Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - The Philippines and American Business & Speech Outline, Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00006; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 1)
    Philippines Politics and government; Philippines Economic Policy; Investments; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks on Argentina at the Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00007; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 1)
    Argentina Politics and government; Argentina Economic policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks on Venezuela at the Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06; MS134.001.001.00008; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 1)
    Venezuela Politics and government; Venezuela Economic policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks on the United Kingdom of Great Britain, Scotland and Wales at the Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06-05; MS134.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Outline-Talk on Middle Africa, Citibank Customers' Overseas Conference, 1959-06-11 -- 1959-06-12; MS134.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - The Dollar as a Reserve Currency, 38th Annual Meeting of the Bankers' Association of Foreign Trade, 1960-05-02; MS134.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Notes for South American Trip, 1960-10; MS134.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - The Dollar Today, The American Chamber of Commerce in Austria, 1961-09-15; MS134.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Remarks at Correspondent Bank Forum, 1962-02-03; MS134.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - How to Succeed in International Business by Really Trying, 20th Stanford Business Conference, 1962-09-14; MS134.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - The Outlook for the Dollar, Insurance Forum, 1962-11-08 -- 1963-01; MS134.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Remarks at the Correspondent Bank Forum, 1963-02-02; MS134.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Remarks at Farrell Ship Launching, 1963-02-16; MS134.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Remarks at Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University, 1963-02-19; MS134.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Remarks at Customers' Conference, 1963-05-22 -- 1963-05-24; MS134.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    Also given at the Council on Foreign Relations, June 7, 1963
  - Never Mind the Noise in the Market, Customers' Overseas Conference, 1963-05-06 -- 1963-08-22; MS134.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - No Royal Road, 48th Annual Meeting of the National Industrial Conference Board, 1964-05-21; MS134.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Far-From What? East-Of Where?, National Association of Manufacturers' 69th Annual Congress of American Industry, 1964-12-03; MS134.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Weighing the Pound, Correspondent Bank Forum, 1965-02-06; MS134.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    Includes presentation slides.
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee on National Security and International Operations of the Committee on Government Operations United States Senate Eighty-Ninth Congress (1 of 2), 1965-05-13 -- 1965-05-25; MS134.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    Testimony at Senator Jackson's Hearings in Washington D.C.
  - Remarks at the American Assembly Arden House, 1965-10-28; MS134.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Diplomacy, Ducks and Dollars, World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1966-05-10; MS134.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - High Cost of Low Insurance, Citibank Insurance Forum, 1966-11-03; MS134.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee on National Security and International Operations of the Committee on Government Operations United States Senate Eighty-Ninth Congress (2 of 2), 1965-05-05 -- 1966-12-07; MS134.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    The speech was given May 13, 1965. Testimony at Senator Jackson's Hearings in Washington D.C.
  - Outline of Remarks at Ninth Training Course of Inter-American Development Bank, 1967-04-07; MS134.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Testimony at the Ways and Means Committee of the House of Representatives, 1967-09-13; MS134.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: An Urban Proposal, New York Commerce and Industry Association, 1967-10-25; MS134.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - How do you do what? FNCB [First National City Bank] Correspondent Bank Forum, 1968-02-03; MS134.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Where Have We Been? And Where Are We Going? And Who's Going to Get Us There?, Harvard Business School, 1968-02-15; MS134.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - The New Servitude, Corporate Management Conference, 1968-04-23; MS134.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - A Long View of the Short Run, International Chamber of Commerce, 1968-10-24; MS134.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Gresham Revisited, World Trade Dinner 55th National Foreign Trade Convention, 1968-11-20; MS134.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    International Trade; Investments; Gresham, Thomas, Sir, 1519?-1579; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969; James, William, 1842-1910
  - Those Were the Days, Correspondent Bank Forum, 1969-02-08; MS134.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Bank Credit Policies-In the Environment of Tomorrow, Reserve City Bankers Association Meeting, 1969-04-01; MS134.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - The Riskless Reexamined, Goldsmiths' Hall London, 1969-05-28; MS134.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Values and the Obligations of Leadership, First National City Bank Board meeting, 1970; MS134.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Nothing Fails Like Success, Correspondent Bank Forum, 1970-02-07; MS134.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Not Every Battle is Armageddon, Texas Bankers Association Annual Convention, 1970-05-05; MS134.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    Banks and banking; Armageddon; Wicker, Tom; Drucker, Peter F. (Peter Ferdinand), 1909-2005; Huntley, Chet, 1911-1974
  - Testimony, U.S. Senate Banking & Currency Committee, 1969-05-20 -- 1970-05-26; MS134.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    The speech was given May 26, 1970.
  - The New "ISM," The American Club, 1971-02-22; MS134.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - R.T. Hon. Geoffrey Rippon Introduction, Harvard Business School International Dinner, 1970-11-20 -- 1971-03-17; MS134.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    The speech was given March 9, 1970.
  - Remarks at World Bank Dinner, 1971-10-04; MS134.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Currency of Change, Citicorp/Citibank Combined Boards Meeting, 1971-10-28; MS134.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - The Modern Pharisee, Religion in American Life Dinner, 1972-03-07; MS134.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - The Global Attic, Bankers Association for Foreign Trade, 1972-05-09; MS134.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Remarks at Harvard Business School Finance Club, 1972-10-26; MS134.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Freedom and Controls, The Insurance Forum, 1972-11-02; MS134.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - The Law of Compensating Forces, The New York Society of Security Analysts, 1973-02-22; MS134.001.002.00019; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 2)
    Citicorp; Bank management; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Dissent of the Majority, The Regional Plan Association, 1973-04-05; MS134.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Remarks at the Annual Meeting of the Economic Development Council, 1973-05-22; MS134.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - The World Corporation-New Weight in an Old Balance, The International Industrial Conference, 1973-09-17; MS134.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    There is an audio CD of a rough draft of this speech in Series 4, box 30, and item #00001.
  - 1973 Captain Robert Dollar Memorial Award, World Trade Dinner-National Foreign Trade Convention, 1973-11-14; MS134.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Remarks at Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. Partners', 1973 -- 1974; MS134.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Competition and the Acephalous Syndrome, Correspondent Bank Forum, 1974-01-26; MS134.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - The Whale Oil, Chicken, and Energy Syndrome, The Economic Club of Detroit, 1974-02-25; MS134.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Remarks at Investor Relations Presentation, 1974-03-05; MS134.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Remarks at Man in Management Award Dinner, 1974-04-02; MS134.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Capital Formation-What is the Question?, The Business Council, 1974-10-12; MS134.001.002.00029; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 2)
    Capital investments; Inflation (Finance) United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Banking with a Difference, Investor Relations Luncheon, 1974-09-25; MS134.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - The World Economy: Dr. Pangloss vs. Jeremiah, The Institute of Directors, 1974-10-25; MS134.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Bess Myerson & Seymour Graubard Introduction, Americanism Dinner, 1974-11-04; MS134.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Even the Future is not What it Used to be, The Commercial Club of Boston, 1974-11-12; MS134.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Blue Eagles and Dj Vu, The Society of American Business Writers, 1975-04-29 -- 1975-05-05; MS134.001.002.00034; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 2)
    The speech was given May 5, 1975.
    United States Economic Policy; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Newton's Law and the Homing Instinct or The Fish are Eating Too Much, The Society of American Business Writers, 1975-05-05; MS134.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Regional Senof Conference [IGB Regional Conference], 1975-07-21 -- 1975-07-24; MS134.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at the American Bankers Association Convention, 1975-10-06; MS134.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - The Ultimate Loophole-Spend Your Own Money, 44th International Conference of the Financial Executives Institute, 1975-10-20; MS134.001.003.00004; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 3)
    Taxation United States; United States Congress; United States Constitution; United States Declaration of Independence; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks and Discussion on Today's Banking Environment, Citibank Correspondent Bank Forum, 1976-01-31; MS134.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Liberty, Leadership and License, The Management Conference University of Chicago Graduate School of Business, 1976-03-11; MS134.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Report on Reorganization, Economic Development Council Luncheon, 1976-04-07; MS134.001.003.00007; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 3)
    New York (N.Y.) Politics and government; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Accounting to Whom for What?, The National Association of Accountants, 1976-06-21; MS134.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - People, Politics, and Productivity: The World Corporation in the 1980's, Multinational Customer Conference, 1976-09-15; MS134.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Topping Out Ceremony Citicorp Center, 1976-10-06; MS134.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony, Saint Peter's Church New York, 1976-10-31; MS134.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Extemporaneous Remarks, ABA Correspondent Banking Conference, 1976-11-08; MS134.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Glass, Steagall, and the Benchley Principle, The Reserve City Bankers Association, 1977-01-31; MS134.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Outlook for the U.S. Economy, Sedlabanki Islands Luncheon, 1977-05-02; MS134.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Let's Create Wealth, Not Allocate Shortages, United Nations Ambassadors Dinner, 1977-05-24; MS134.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Warning: The Law May Be Hazardous to Society's Health, American College of Trial Lawyers, 1977-08-06; MS134.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Introduction of Robert S. Strauss & Variations on a Theme: Informal Remarks, International Industrial Conference, 1977-09-12 -- 1977-09-15; MS134.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at the Tri-State United Way, 1977-09-30; MS134.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Testimony, New York State Assembly Committee on Banking-Cincotta Hearings, 1975-03-11 -- 1977-10-11; MS134.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
    The speech was given October 11, 1977.
  - Panel on International Trade, Business Council Meeting, 1977-10-14; MS134.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Protecting Trade from Protectionism, Brussels, 1977-10-24; MS134.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Urban Affairs Luncheon Meeting, 1977-11-21; MS134.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at National Foreign Trade Convention, 1977-11-14; MS134.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Welcoming Remarks, Investor Relations Presentation to Security Analysts, 1978-03-28; MS134.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Business Council Meeting, 1978-05-12; MS134.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Twenty-Fifth International Monetary Conference, 1978-05-23; MS134.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - The Oil Shock Plus 5! A Reassessment, U.S. Chamber of Commerce of Sao Paulo, 1978-09-14; MS134.001.003.00027; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 3)
    Economics.; Petroleum industry and trade; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at IMG [Investment Management Group] Lawyers' Dinner, 1978-10-17; MS134.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Remarks at Conference on Employee Mental Wellness, 1978-12-01; MS134.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Domestic International Banking Units, The New School Banking Course, 1979-03-19; MS134.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Wriston--Wharton, Wharton School Club, 1979-03-20; MS134.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - The Other Nine Amendments, American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1979-05-02; MS134.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Information, Electronics and Gold, International Monetary Conference, 1979-06-11; MS134.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at United Way of Tri-State Luncheon, 1979-09-20; MS134.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Risk and Other Four-Letter Words, The Economic Club of Chicago, 1979-10-25; MS134.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Chrysler Corporation Statement, Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, 1979-11-21; MS134.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Clifton Garvin Introduction, Eagle Scout Award Dinner, 1980; MS134.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at the Financial Accounting Standards Board at the Public Hearing on Accounting by Debtors and Creditors When Debt is Restructured, 1980; MS134.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at the International Monetary Fund, 1980; MS134.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at Retirement Dinner of Reginald Jones (G.E.), 1980; MS134.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - From the Hall of Mirrors to the Floppy Disc, National Bureau of Economic Research, 1980-01-03; MS134.001.004.00010; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 4)
    Technology; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Let's Stop Making the Wrong Mistakes, 1980 Banking Forum, 1980-01-26; MS134.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Welcoming Remarks, Security Analysts Annual Briefing, 1980-03-25; MS134.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Looking Backward at the Nineteen-Eighties, Reserve City Bankers, 1980-03-31; MS134.001.004.00013; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 4)
    Banks and banking; Competition; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Price vs. Policy: A Tale of Two Markets, International Trade Conference, 1980-04-08; MS134.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Is Inflation a Handshake Deal?, Tom Storrs Testimonial, 1980-05-07; MS134.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at United Way of Tri-State Recognition Luncheon, 1980-05-12; MS134.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - The Consent of the Governed - Add Your Own Two Cents Worth, API Financial Officers' Meeting, 1980-06-10; MS134.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - If it Works, Don't Fix It: Euromarket Controls, Swiss-American Chamber of Commerce, 1980-09-22; MS134.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at the Paris Chamber of Commerce, 1980-09-24; MS134.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Acceptance Speech for the Civic Commitment Award, Anti-Defamation League, 1980-10-07; MS134.001.004.00020 (Box 4)